<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Piper Williams | Blog</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Piper Williams | Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Certifications OSCP GWAPT Metasploit Pro Certified Leadership Women in Security - Kansas City Communications Board Member
Job Experience Lead Threat &amp;amp; Vulnerability Analyst - Deloitte Security Engineer, Cloud Security Resilence Engineering Team - H&amp;amp;R Block Application Security Enginner - H&amp;amp;R Block Lead Developer - Yellow Education Bachelors of Science in Information Security Engineering - University of Missouri</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Blob Storage &#43; .NET Client Library</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/azureblobstorage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/azureblobstorage/</guid>
      <description>Azure offers Blob Storage as the cloud storage solution. Blob Storage is a way of storing substantial amounts of unstructured data: data that doesn&amp;rsquo;t adhere to a specific data model or definition- data that can&amp;rsquo;t go into rows and columns. For example, video, audio, image, log files, text files, etc. Azure Blob Storage has three types of resources to offer:
The Storage Account Container(s) within the storage account Blob(s) within the Container Prerequisites Azure Subscription Azure Storage Account The current .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use a Windows VM system-assigned managed identity to access Azure Storage via a SAS credential</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Assigning TLS1.2 to Storage Account and VM
Adding the VM to the firewall subnet inclusions
Create a System Managed Identity and assign to VM
Give that System Managed Identity RBAC over the storage account
Azure PowerShell Modules Install-Module AzureRM Install-Module Azure -AllowClobber Install-Module Az -AllowClobber #AllowClobber flag removes the overlap between AzureRM, Az, and Azure PS Modules’ conflicting command names. PowerShell Script TLS1.2 can be set it the portal settings as well – following command must have Admin privs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
